

······Contact

mihretab.habtemichael@motopp.nl Web - https://github.com/Z-Michael

HYWW 'Skills'

Mendix HTML CSS VJj UgWfJdh 6cchghfUd K cfXdfYgg G'UW CZZW '* \$

GcZhG_]``g

GY`ZAchij UhYX HYUa d`UmYf 8YV|kg]cb AU_er Waaib]cator

Languages^{*}

Nederlands (6%) English(9I W``Ybh)



Mihreteab Habtemichael

Netherlands, Hilversum

Profile

I am a self trained frontend web developer. I am fascinated by Web technologies and programming languages. I have Studied Python Programming with three certificates. Not only that, but I also made few websites for myself and exercised the programming languages that i have studied like JavaScript, HTML and CSS. Since January, I got a wonderful opportunity to be a Mendix developer. Mendix is the future platform for website technologies with a multi functionality and flexibility platform. I am so passionate to learn and to show my skills in teams and add values.

Motopp Mendix Advanced Developer Accelerator Program

202

We have been taught to use the Mendix platform. We have built a Mendix app from scratch, where we had to collaborate with a Product Owner to finalize the requirements and convert those into a working and business/user centric application. While executing the project we have joined several Mendix courses and lectures for further knowledge extension. Which was directly put into practice in their Mendix project.

- Certification
- Agile working
- ALMÁ
- Team Server
- VersioningÁ
- BranchingÁ
- DomainÁ modellingÁ
- DataÁ normalizationÁ

- Security verification
- Account handling
- Front-endÁ developmentÁ
- Page buildingÁ
- Data bindingÁ
- ' StylingÁ
- Microflow modellingÁ

- Data processing
- Data generation
- QueryingÁ
- Integration Rest,Á Excel, filingÁ
- Modelling bestÁ practicingÁ
- Process modelling
- Action orientatedÁ modellingÁ

Education

* &\$\$, !20%((Ethiopia))!6UW(Y`cf`cZ7ca di hYf`5dd`]\Wh]cbg` fEquivalent to Netherlands <6C LevelŁ

Certificates

- * Python Fundamental
- * Python Data Structure
- * Python Data Base

Work Experience

- * 2011-2012 (*Ethiopia*) -Worked as a Library Network Administrator.
- * 2020-2021 as a WordPress Developer
- * Monitoring website performance and handling troubleshooting and News feed update . https://educationrunway.nl/nl/
- * 2020-2021- Junior AI-Operator at MediaPark.

Voluntarily Jobs

- * Education Runaway(https://educationrunway.nl/nl/) board member.
- * Computer and Smart phones installation/Maintenance.
- * Translation language from Tigregna to Dutch/English.
- * Basic computer Training for Eritrean Residences in Hilversum

My Background

I came to The Netherlands around 2013. I had a long Asylum procedure and It was a rough time to accomplish my dreams. At Asylum seekers center i have been helping on translating and teaching other refugees a basic computers skills. Since 2018 i got my residence permit and my life got back on track. I started learning Dutch and focused on self studying (web develop ment) and related ICT technologies While i am doing self development; I started to look for a new, promising field in which I would take great pleasure to improve myself and where i could build something. And as the great chance of my life, I met Motopp. Mendix is exactly what I was looking for and started my journey on 2022 as Mendix Developer.